Okay, I checked.
좋아요, 확인해봤는데요
We have Earl Grey, English Breakfast,
Cinnamon Stick...
얼 그레이, 영국식 아침 식사,
시나몬 스틱, 카밀레, 민트 메들리,
...Chamomile, Mint Medley,
Blackberry and
블랙 베리, 그리고...
하나 더 있는데, 레몬 수더!
Wait, there's one more.
Lemon Soother!
You're not the guy that asked
for tea, are you?
차 주문하신 분 아니죠?
그래요
The One Where The Monkey Gets Away
우편물 왔어요, 레이첼 그린
우편물이요
Mail call!
Rachel Greene, bunk seven.
고마워
Thank you.
Oh, cool!
A free sample of coffee.
신난다, 커피 무료 쿠폰이야
Oh, good. Because where else
would we get any?
잘됐네
공짜 커피를 어디서 먹겠어?
그러게
맞는 말이야
Oh, right.
-Oh, great.
-What is it?
- 이런...
- 뭔데?
Country club newsletter.
컨트리 클럽 소식지
My mother sends me the engagement
notices for inspiration.
엄마가 약혼 소식란을 보냈어
나 충격 받으라고
Oh, my God! It's Barry and Mindy!
세상에...
배리하고 민디야
Barry, who you almost
- 네가 찼던 배리?
- 내가 찼던 배리
- 네 들러리 민디?
- 내 들러리 민디
And Mindy, your maid of
좀 보자
Let me see. That's Mindy?
이 여자가 민디야?
예쁘다
She is pretty!
Lucky...
잘됐다구
...to have had a friend like you.
너 같은 친구를 뒀잖아
그럼 난... 가볼게
Now it's quiet time.
마르셀, 쌀 가져와
쌀 가져와
Marcel, bring me the rice. Come on.
착하다, 그렇지
쌀 가져와
Good boy. Give me the rice.
고마워, 잘했어
Thank you. Good boy.
드디어 '가져와'와 '가서 싸'란
말의 차이를 가르쳤지
He's mastered the difference between
"bring me the" and "pee in the."
'가져와'란 말이랑...
레이첼?
"Bring me the" and
Rach?
- 뭐?
- 뭐해?
미안해
정말 이해가 안 가
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is so stupid!
난 배리를 포기했잖아
I mean, I gave Barry up, right?
두 사람을 위해 기뻐해야
한다구, 난 기뻐
I should be happy for them.
I am. I'm happy for them.
- 정말?
- 아니
-Really?
-No.
나한테 남자가 있다면
이러지 않겠지
I guess it would be different
if I were with somebody.
남자는 절대 안 사귄다고
했던 게 누구였더라?
Whoa, what....
What happened to "Forget
relationships! I'm done with men!"
"남자라면 질색이야
물건 달린 인종은 다 싫어"
The whole penis embargo?
모르겠어
I don't know.
남자가 싫다는 게 아니라
제대로 된 짝을 만나겠단 얘기야
It's not about no guys.
It's about the right guy.
배리하고 있을 땐 마음이
놓이고 편했지만 열정이 없었어
With Barry it was safe and easy,
but there was no heat.
하지만 파올로하고는
열정뿐이었지
With Paolo, all there was, was heat.
짐승처럼 격렬한 열정 말야
-lt was this raw, animal, sexual
-Right. I got it.
알아, 알고 있어
나도 눈이 있어
I was there.
둘 다를 가질 순 없는 걸까?
Do you think you can have both?
친구처럼 지내면서 발가락을
간지럽힐 수 있는 그런 남자를...
Someone who's your best friend
but also can make your toes curl.
그래, 알아
나도 그래
Yes.
Yes, I do. I really do.
좀 우습긴 한데
생각지도 못했던 사람이
In fact, it's funny.
Often, someone
you wouldn't think could...
발가락을 간지럽혀줄 수도
있어, 그러니까...
...curl your toes...
... might just be the one who...
- 안녕
- 방해꾼이 나타났네, 안녕
...gets interrupted.
영화는 어땠어?
How was the movie?
- 좋았어
- 굉장했어
-Wonderful!
-So good!
- 못 봐주겠더라
- 완전 꽝이었어
-Suck fest.
-Total chick flick.
물론 너희가 좋아하는 영화는
아니었을 거야
I'm sorry it wasn't one of those
movies with guns and bombs...
총이나 폭탄, 무섭게 달리는
버스도 안 나오니까
...and buses going really fast!
영화를 즐기는 데 폭력이
필요한 건 아냐
I don't need violence
in a movie...
누드만 나오면
...as long as
there's a little nudity.
- 누드 나왔잖아
- 남자 누드 말고
-There was nudity.
-I meant female nudity.
루 그랜트의 벗은 몸
같은 건 보기 싫었다구
I don't need to see
Lou Grant frolicking.
휴 그랜트야
Hugh! Hugh Grant!
좋아, 난 가야겠다
All right, I've got to go.
가자, 마르셀
이리 온
Come on, Marcel.
가서 목욕해야지
맞지? 그래
We're gonna go take a bath.
Yes, we are, aren't we?
쟤들 아직 친구 맞아?
They're still just friends, right?
그럼 내일 보자
And I will see you tomorrow.
그래, 내일은 레이첼 고모랑
노는 거야, 알지?
You're gonna spend
tomorrow at Aunt Rachel's.
잠깐, 모니카 고모는
아무 말 못 들었는데?
Does Aunt Monica get a say in this?
모니카 고모, 질투하는 거야?
Please, Aunt Monica, please?
그럴 자격이 있나?
여기 있지도 않을 거면서
Unclench. You're not even
gonna be here.
우리가 이런 얘길 하게
될 줄은 생각도 못했어
-I can't believe we're discussing this.
-I agree. I'm, like, in disbelief.
그래, 나도 믿기지가 않아
레이첼하고 잘 맺어지려면
벌써 그런 눈치가 있지 않았을까?
If it was gonna happen,
wouldn't it have happened already?
나같은 사람과 사귀고 싶다고
분명히 얘기했어
She said she wants a relationship
with someone exactly like me.
정말 그렇게 말했어?
She said that?
아니, 나 같은 사람이란 말은
내가 덧붙인 거지만
I added the exactly like me" part.
누군가를 찾고 있는데
그 누군가와 오늘밤을 보낼 거야
But she's looking for someone.
And someone will be there tonight.
- 오늘밤?
- 오늘밤
"Tonight" tonight?
정말 좋은 기회야
단둘이서 보낼 거거든
It's perfect.
It'll just be the two of us.
하루종일 내 원숭이를
봐주기로 했어
She spent all day
taking care of my monkey.
지난번에 원숭이 봐주던
여자랑은 어떻게 됐더라?
I can't remember the last time
a girl took care of my monkey.
어쨌든, 퇴근하면서
와인 한 병을 사 갖고
Anyway, I figured after work,
I'd pick up some wine...
집에 가서 허전한 마음을
달래줄 거야
...go over there and try to woo her.
- 내가 좋은 방법 가르쳐 줘?
- 뭔데?
Know what you should do?
네 구닥다리 방법이 통하는
1890년대로 돌아가는 거야
Take her back to the 1 890s
when that phrase was last used.
계속 고집 피우다간
끝장을 보게 만들어 주겠어
If you keep this up, you'll be
finished by the weekend.
저기 깃털 달린 보아뱀 두른
사람이 프란시스 박사야
The one in the feathered boa
is Dr. Francis.
원래 남자였어
Now, she used to be a man.
저기 봐, 레이븐이다
저 여자 너무 싫어
Look, there's Raven.
We hate her. We're glad she's dying.
병 걸려서 죽을 거래
그리고 있잖아...
마르셀
And then
What? Marcel!
모니카 신발 물어뜯게?
그럼 안돼
Are you playing with Monica's shoes?
You're not supposed to
이런, 이런, 마르셀
너 구두에 똥 눴어?
Marcel, did you poo in the shoe?
마르셀, 나쁜 원숭이
맙소사...
Oh, Marcel! Bad monkey!
Oh, God!
미안해, 배리
약혼 선물로 받아줘
Sorry, Barry.
A little engagement gift.
마음의 선물이야
I'm sure you didn't
register for that.
누가 죽었어?
Who died? Who died?
뒤집어봐
빨리 좀 뒤집어봐
Roll him over!
Come on, roll him over!
덱스터는 아니구나
그렇지, 마르셀?
Well, we know it wasn't Dexter,
right, Marcel? Because
마르셀, 마르셀, 마르...
Marcel?
어쩌다 잃어버렸어?
-How could you lose him?
-I don't know!
나도 몰라, TV 보고 있는데
모니카 구두에 똥을 눴더라구
We were watching TV,
he pooped in Monica's shoe....
잠깐, 내 구두에?
Wait. He pooped in my shoe?
Which one?
어느 거?
몰라, 왼쪽일 거야
I don't know. The left one!
어느 거?
Which ones?
Those little clunky Amish things
you think go with everything.
너 맨날 신고 다니는
투박한 구두 있잖아
- 안녕?
- 어서와
이 방 분위기가 왜
이렇게 부정적이니?
Why is the air in here so negative?
레이첼이 마르셀을
잃어버렸대
Rachel lost Marcel.
설마, 어쩌다?
Oh, no! How?
내 구두에 똥 눴대
-He pooped in my shoe.
-Which one?
어느 거?
내가 항상 신고 다니는
귀여운 검은 구두 있잖아
The cute black ones I always wear.
어느 쪽?
No, which one?
오른쪽이야 왼쪽이야?
The right or left?
왼쪽이면 행운이 있는 거래
Because the left one is lucky.
어떻게 하지?
어쩌면 좋아?
Come on!
What am I gonna do?
좋아, 원숭이가 되서 생각해봐
도시에서 길을 잃었어
All right. You're a monkey.
You're loose in the city.
어디로 갈래?
Where do you go?
생전 처음 나간 거니까
도시 투어 중일 거야
It's his first time out,
so he'll do touristy things.
나 같으면 '캣츠'나
'러시아 응접실'을 보러 가겠다
I'll go to Cats.
You go to the Russian Tea Room.
장난하지 말고
어떻게 좀 해봐
Oh, my God!
Come on, you guys!
곧 집에 올 텐데
로스가 알면 날 죽일 거야
He'll be home any minute.
He's gonna kill me!
이 건물부터 시작하자
너희는 1, 2층을 찾아
Search the building. Take the first
floor. We'll take the rest.
피비랑 난 3, 4층을 맡을게
그럼 난 뭐해?
난 뭐하고 있어?
What am I gonna do?
넌 전화기 옆에서
기다리고 있어
You stay here
and wait by the phone.
내 구두에 스프레이 뿌리고
오빠 와서 널 죽이기나 기다려
Spray Lysol in my shoe
and wait for Ross to kill you.
누가 나랑 안 바꿀래?
Does anybody want to trade?
뭐야?
What do you want?
헤클스 씨, 제 친구가 원숭이를
잃어버렸는데 보셨어요?
Mr. Heckles, have you seen a monkey?
밖에 와플 내놨는데
아가씨가 가져갔지?
I left a Belgian waffle out here.
Did you take it?
아뇨
왜 와플을 복도에 내놨어요?
-Why'd you leave it in the hall?
-I wasn't ready for it.
먹을 준비가 안됐거든
원숭이 못 보셨어요?
Have you seen a monkey?
쥐새끼 한 마리 못 봤어
I saw Regis Philbin once.
감사합니다, 헤클스 씨
Thank you, Mr. Heckles.
와플 갚아야 돼
You owe me a waffle.
얼굴이 하얀 흰목꼬리감기
원숭이인데요...
He's a black capuchin monkey
with a white face...
러시안 드레싱하고
피클도 갖다주세요
...with Russian dressing
and pickles on the side.
네, 고마워요
Thanks.
- 안녕?
- 안녕, 오늘 어땠어?
How did it go today?
- 좋았어
- 정말?
Oh, great!
It went great. Really great.
정말 좋았어, 재밌었구
와인이야?
Is that wine?
그래
마실래?
You want some?
- 마시고 싶어
- 그래?
Oh, I would love some.
근데 말야
여기서 마시지 말자
But let's not drink it here.
기분이 좀 이상한데
우리, 뉴워크에 갈래?
I'm feeling crazy.
You wanna go to Newark?
좋아,
물론 갈 수야 있지만
Okay, but before we head off to
the murder capital of the Northeast...
거기 갔다 재수없게
죽을지 모르니까
우선 하고 싶은 말이 있어
... I kind of wanted
to run something by you.
전에 했던 얘기 말인데...
남자를 사귀는 문제 말야
You know how we
were talking before...
...about relationships, and stuff.
로스, 아무래도 안되겠어
-Oh, God, Ross, I cannot do this!
-Okay, quick and painful.
그래, 대답 한번 빠르구나
맙소사, 좋아
괜찮아, 그래
Oh, God!
Okay, all right.
All right, okay.
로스, 나 미워하지 마
Please don't hate me.
왜, 무슨 일인데?
What?
마르셀 알지?
You know Marcel?
알지
내가 마르셀을...
잃어버린 것 같아
I kind of lost him.
어떻게 그럴 수가 있어?
I can't believe this.
밖에 못 나가게만
해달라고 했는데
All I asked you to do was
keep him in here!
알아, 정말 미안해
I know. I'm sorry.
아니, 내 잘못도 있어
It's partially my fault.
펜이나 연필도 아닌데 원숭이를
봐달라고 한 내가 잘못한 거지
I shouldn't have had you
start with a monkey.
You should have started
with a pencil.
무슨 일이든 할게
지금 다들 찾으러 갔으니까...
I'm doing everything I can.
Everyone's looking for him and I got
누구세요?
-Who is it?
-Animal Control.
동물 보호 센터예요
- 봐, 동물 보호 센터도 왔잖아
- 동물 보호 센터를 불렀어?
-I've even got Animal Control.
-You called Animal Control?
응...
왜, 싫어?
Why? Do you not like them?
마르셀은...
불법 외래 동물이야
Marcel is an illegal exotic animal.
국내에서 키우면 안돼
I'm not allowed to have him. If they
find him, they'll take him away.
마르셀을 찾으면
데리고 갈 거라구
그런 얘기한 적 없잖아
Well, now, see,
you never ever told us that.
집으로 동물 보호 센터를
불러들일 줄 몰랐으니까
Because I never expected you
to invite them to the apartment!
와줘서 고마워요
Thanks for coming.
원숭이 때문에 전화했죠?
Somebody called about a monkey?
아뇨, 어처구니없는 오해가
있었지 뭐예요
You know, that was
a complete misunderstanding.
원숭이인줄 알았는데
아닌 거 있죠?
We thought we had a monkey,
but we didn't.
알고보니까 모자더라구요
-Turned out it was a hat.
-Cat!
- 고양이
- 고양이요, 내가 뭐랬어?
3, 4층 다 찾아봤는데
마르셀을 못 봤대
We checked, no one's seen Marcel.
- 마르셀?
- 마르셀 삼촌이요
-My uncle Marcel.
-ls that who the monkey's named after?
삼촌 이름을 따서
원숭이 이름을 지었구나?
좋아요,
불법 외래 동물을 키우면
Possession of an illegal exotic
is punishable...
2년 이하의 징역과 원숭이
압수에 들어가게 돼있어요
... by two years in prison
and confiscation of the animal.
세상에, 그 가엾은 걸
감옥에 처넣는다구요?
Oh, my God!
You'd put that poor
little creature in jail?
피비, 말하기 전에 우선 속으로
생각해보란 말 잊었어?
Remember how we talked about saying
things quietly to yourself first?
항상 그럴 순 없잖아
Yes, but there isn't always time.
뭔가 해결책이 있을 거예요
앉으세요
I'm sure there's some friendly way
to reconcile this. Have a seat.
우선 소개부터 하죠
전 모니카 겔러예요
We haven't met. I'm Monica Geller.
세상에, 너구나
Oh, my God, you are!
- 넌 레이첼 그린이고
- 네
And you're Rachel Greene!
루이사 지아네트야
링컨 고교 동창
Luisa Gianetti! Lincoln High?
홈룸 시간에 너희들
뒷자리에 앉았어
I sat behind you guys in homeroom.
루이사, 세상에
Luisa! Oh, my God!
모니카, 루이사래
Monica! It's Luisa!
나도 거기 나왔어요
I went there too!
- 그래, 루이사, 홈룸 시간
- 그래
Luisa! From homeroom!
내가 누군지 모르는 거지?
You have no idea who I am, do you?
- 그래
- 모르겠어
-No.
-Not at all.
하긴, 4년 동안 너희는
날 완전히 무시했으니까
Well, maybe that's because
you spent four years ignoring me.
'안녕, 루이사'란 인사 한마디가
그렇게 힘들었어?
Would it have been hard to say,
"Morning, Luisa"...
'안녕, 뚱땡아'란 인사도?
...or "Nice overalls"?
정말 미안해
Oh, I'm so sorry!
넌 그나마 괜찮아
너도 뚱보라 힘들었을 거야
It's not so much you. You were fat.
You had your own problems.
근데 넌!
정말 재수없어
But you. What a bitch!
뭐?
What?
흥분하지 말자
You know what? Be that as it may...
옛정을 생각해서 우리 좀
도와주지 않을래?
...could you help us with the
monkey thing, for old times'sake?
우린 친구잖아
Go, Bobcats!
그럴 순 있지만, 싫어
I could. But I won't.
원숭이를 찾으면 압수야
If I find that monkey, he's mine.
미안
Sorry.
마르셀?
Marcel?
마르셀
- 마르셀
안녕, 무슨 일이죠?
Hi, can I help you?
지금 비상 사태인데요
뭘 찾고 있어요
We're having an emergency,
and we were looking for something.
원숭이요
-A monkey.
-Yes, have you seen any?
혹시 보셨어요?
아뇨, 못 봤어요
No, I haven't seen a monkey.
라디에이터 고칠 줄 알아요?
Can you fix radiators?
그럼요, 손잡이를 반대쪽으로
돌려봤어요?
Sure! Did you try turning the knob
back the other way?
그럼요
그럼, 몰라요
-Of course!
-Oh. Then, no.
맛 좀 볼래?
럼이 너무 많이 들어갔나봐
-Taste this. Is there too much rum?
-Just a second.
잠깐만,
원숭이 꼭 찾으세요
-Hope you find your monkey.
-No, wait!
아니, 잠깐만요
라디에이터에 대해서는
잘 모르지만
We may not know about radiators...
온도 조절하는 문제에는
저희가 일가견이 있는데요
... but we do have expertise
in the heating and cooling milieu.
우리 지금 하던 일이 있잖아
Aren't we in the middle of something?
이 여자분들이 더우시다잖아
우리가 도와야지
But these women are very hot,
and they need our help.
많이 더워보이는데
And they're very hot!
안돼
We can't, all right?
미안합니다
We're sorry.
정말 미안한데요
원숭이를 찾는다고 약속했어요
You don't know how sorry.
We promised to find this monkey.
키가 이만하고 마르셀이라고
부르면 대답할 거예요
He's this high
and answers to the name Marcel.
사진이 있으면 우릴 도울 수
있을 텐데 아쉽네요
So if we could get pictures of you,
it'd help us out.
이제부터 입만 벌려봐라
From now on, you don't get
to talk to other people.
- 마르셀?
- 마르셀!
- 위험 - 고압
- 마르셀?
- 마르셀
- 난 몰라!
- 왜?
-Oh, my God!
-What?
- 뭐가 내 오른발에 닿았어
- 뭔데?
Something brushed up
against my right leg.
괜찮아, 내 왼발이야
Oh, it's okay.
It was just my left leg.
저기 봐
Look, Phoebe!
마르셀, 이리 온
이리 와
Oh, Marcel! Come here!
가만있어
Step aside, ladies.
뭐하는 거야?
-What are you gonna do?
-Just a tranquilizer.
마취 총이야
도망쳐, 마르셀
도망쳐!
Run, Marcel, run!
제길!
Damn!
괜찮아?
-Are you okay?
-I think so.
그래, 괜찮아...
맙소사
Oh, gosh!
- 마르셀?
- 마르셀
마르셀? 이럴 순 없어
We've been all over the neighborhood!
He's just gone!
온 동네를 뒤져봤는데 없잖아
아주 가버린 거야
아직 모르잖아
-You don't know that.
-It's cold, it's dark.
춥고 어두운데 마르셀은
이곳 지리도 모른단 말야
He doesn't know the Village!
발까지 다쳤잖아
이런...
And now I have a broken foot.
I have no monkey and a broken foot!
원숭이는 없어지고 발만
다쳤어, 네 덕분이야
Thank you very much!
로스, 미안하다고
수백 번도 더 말했어
I've said I'm sorry a million times.
내가 어떡했으면 좋겠어?
What do you want me to do?
어떻게 할까?
내 발도 다쳐야겠어?
You want me to break my foot too?
I'll break it right now.
좋아, 나도 다치면 되잖아
아, 아파라...
이제 만족해?
Oh, my God!
There, are you happy now?
그래, 네 발도 다치니까
Yeah, now that you kicked the sign...
마르셀이 하나도
안 보고싶다
... I don't miss Marcel anymore!
일부러 그런 것도 아니잖아
It's not like
I did this on purpose.
넌 원래 이런 식이야
No, this is just vintage Rachel.
너한테는 항상 사고가
일어난다구
Things just sort of happen around you!
넌 '레이첼' 왕국에서
'레이첼' 식으로 살고 있어
You're off in "Rachel Land,"
doing your "Rachel Thing"...
원숭이든 사람의 감정이든
넌 아무 관심이 없지
...oblivious to people's monkeys
or to people's feelings and
- 로스?
- 아무 소리 하지 마
I don't want to hear it!
Forget it, okay?
- 로스
- 넌 항상... 관두자
- 로스?
- 뭐? 뭐?
What?
- 이봐요
- 바나나 장사, 잠깐!
Hey, banana man!
정말 신기하다
This is so intense!
엉덩이 한쪽은 잠들었는데
다른 쪽은 아무 것도 모르고 있어
One side of my butt is totally asleep
and the other side has no idea.
왜 이래?
-What's with Phoebe?
-Tranquilizer dart.
- 마취 총 맞았어
- 어쩐지
바나나 시키셨어요?
Hi! Did you order some bananas?
- 그럼 안돼?
- 내 원숭이 돌려줘요
-What about it?
-Give me my monkey back!
원숭이 없어
-I don't have a monkey.
-Then what's with the bananas?
이 바나나는 뭐죠?
몸에 좋잖아
Potassium.
마르셀, 마르셀
어디 있죠?
어디 있어요?
마르셀, 마르셀?
Okay, where is he?
시간 낭비하지 마
You're wasting your time.
왜, 왜?
What?
마르셀!
마르셀
얘한테 무슨 짓을 한 거예요?
-What have you done to him?
-That's my monkey. That's Patty.
내 원숭이야, 패티지
원숭이 패티
미쳤어요?
이리 와, 마르셀, 어서
Are you insane? Come here, Marcel.
이리 와, 패티
Come here, Patty.
이리 와, 마르셀
Come here, Marcel.
이리 와, 패티
이리 온, 원숭아
이리 온
Come here, Patty.
Here, monkey.
Here, monkey!
잡았다
Gotcha!
- 내 원숭이 돌려줘요
- 내 원숭이야
-Give me my monkey back!
-It's mine.
두 사람 다 법정에 설
준비나 해요
Take this up with the judge.
내 원숭이 아냐
That's not my monkey. The dress
is mine. Send it back whenever.
옷만 내 거지
나중에 다시 보내줘
- 내 원숭이 내놔요
- 안돼요
All right, I want my monkey!
부탁이야, 루이사
-Oh, come on, Luisa.
-Sorry, prom queen.
미안하다, 댄스 퀸
넌 뚱보가 못돼서
재수없는 퀸이 됐을 거야
You had to be a bitch in school,
instead of fat.
좋아, 난 고등학교 때
댄스 퀸, 동창회 퀸이었어
In high school, I was prom queen...
...and the homecoming queen and you...
반장도 했고, 그리고 넌...
같은 반이었지
...were also there.
하지만 이건 고등학교가
아니라, 현실이야
But this isn't high school.
We're all adults here!
우린 어른이잖아
헤클스 씨, 이거 봐요
Heckles! Can I have this?
부탁이야
For the most part.
네가 원숭이를 데려가면
난 소중한 사람들을 잃게 돼
If you take this monkey, I'll lose
an important person in my life.
날 미워해도 좋지만
이 친구를 벌하진 말아줘
You can hate me if you want,
but please do not punish him.
좀 더 큰 사람이 될 수
있는 기회야
You have a chance
to be the bigger person here.
기회를 잡으라구
Take it!
싫어
No.
좋아
All right. Then I'll call
your supervisor and tell her...
그럼 네가 내 친구 엉덩이에
마취 총 쐈다고 신고할 거야
...you shot my friend with a dart!
이 옷 좀 벗자
싫으면 그냥 입든가, 좋아
It'll be nice to get this off,
won't it?
Or we can leave it on. That's fine.
저기다 구두만 신기면
정말 환상이겠다
With the right pumps,
that would be a great little outfit.
너한테 심하게 군 거 미안해
난 그냥...
Listen, I'm sorry I was so hard
on you before
아냐, 다 내 잘못인걸
네 원숭이를 잃어버렸잖아
No, it was my fault.
I almost lost your
아냐, 그래도 네가 다시
찾아줬잖아
Yeah, but you got him back.
You were great.
정말 대단했어
근데 말야, 와인이 아직
그대로 있는데
We still have that bottle of wine.
어때, 한 잔 할래?
Are you in the mood
for something grape?
- 좋아
- 그래
마시자
-Sure, that would be good.
-All right.
좋아
어디서 전기 공사하나보네
The neighbors must be vacuuming.
이렇게 앉아 있으니까...
Well, as long as we're here...
뭐랄까...
...and not on the subject....
생각해봤는데
I was thinking about...
우리가 너무 화가 나있었지?
... how mad we got
at each other before.
근데...
그건 우리가 서로에게...
And maybe it was partially
because of how we
- 레이첼?
- 배리?
-Rachel?
-Barry?
아무래도 안되겠어
나 민디랑 결혼 못해
I can't do it.
I can't marry Mindy.
아직도 자기를 사랑해
I think I'm still in love with you.
문부터 잠그는 건데
We have got to start
locking that door!
- 좀 보자
- 그래, 뭐 어때
Show us! Come on!
좋아, 알았어
-lt was such a long time ago.
-Okay, fine. All right.
'사운드 오브 뮤직' 할 때야
아이들 보여?
This is me in The Sound of Music.
See the von Trapp kids?
아니
내가 맨 앞에 서서 그래
That's because I'm in front of them.
엄청나네
Big nun!
난 산이 버티고 있는 줄
알았어
I thought that was an alp.
고등학교 시절은
기억하고 싶지 않아
High school wasn't
my favorite time.
글쎄, 난 그때가 좋은데
I loved high school.
4년 동안 파티에 데이트에
섹스에...
It was four years of parties,
dating and sex and
난 남학생 4백 명이랑
기숙사에서 살았어
Well, I went to boarding school
with 400 boys.
섹스 한번 했다간
신세 망쳤을 거야
Any sex I had would've involved
a major lifestyle choice.
몇백 년은 된 것 같지 않니?
Doesn't it seem like
a million years ago?
엉덩이가 살아나고 있어
My butt cheek is waking up!